All right, Arrow, who are we
adding to our ranks today?
So he's the lucky soul?
That boy there will be the sixth
new stand user I've created.
It doesn't seem real, but I've
conscripted a formidable crew.
And using their might, I'll eliminate any
miscreant who comes after my Yoshikage!
What the?
Huh?
Ow. That hurt. What?
That's never happened before.
I'm positive that the arrow chose him.
But it was deflected.
In the heart of the heart,
the light of the light!
The light of the spirit,
Let the voice of love take you higher.
Every piece of intel we could
find on him is in that envelope.
Gotta hand it to the bastard who's done
a damn fine job of covering his tracks.
Curse you, Kira.
What's your new name?
And whose face have you stolen?
Where are you?
It's summer.
The way I hear it, this is
tourist season in Morioh.
Yeah.
I doubt he'll be able to
resist his urges for long.
That son of a bitch will be
itching to kill real soon.
Summertime has finally arrived!
And if you hadn't noticed,
July 1st was the opening of Morioh's
beautiful rivers and beaches.
With tourists descending on
us from S-City and beyond,
our little old Morioh is really hopping.
Whether you're getting
a little R &R, camping,
fishing, or yachting, consider
Morioh your special summer paradise.
Now, how's everyone going to
make the most of this season?
Yes, quite the summer paradise.
And not just for the morally upright.
Everyone wanted to enjoy the season.
We're all forced to live out our lives
concealing our deepest hopes and fears.
But to forever keep them to yourself,
can one truly live out their days
behind such a veil of secrecy?
Damn it.
All I want is for that girl to
see the true Yoshikage Kira.
To hear the passion that burns within me.
To feel my hands wrapped around her tender
neck as I Ring the life from her body.
As my nails grow, so do my carnal desires.
I just need to persevere
until the urge subsides.
For now, I should practice this signature.
I still haven't mastered it.
Jousuke Higashikata.
Jotorel Kujo.
They're the reason I'm
in this predicament.
Evening.
So dear, what are you doing now?
Oh, wow, silly me.
I should have just used my eyes.
You're in the middle of reading a book.
I thought you might enjoy a cup of tea.
I know I don't normally
do this type of thing,
but I thought I'd try something different.
So here it is.
If you don't want any, that's fine too.
Oh, my, would you look at the time.
I suppose I should hit the sack.
Do it.
Bear your heart to her.
Show her your true self.
Yoshikage Kira!
Harry!
Shit!
Baring my soul was a mistake.
They'll figure me out at this rate.
Sorry for the scare.
Forgive me.
Wait.
Was he trying to unbutton
my dress just now?
He apologized for scaring me.
No, baby, you have
nothing to be sorry about.
This new you is something else.
I don't know where it's coming
from, but it's turning me on.
I never thought I'd say this, but I
think I've fallen in love with you.
Hey, Josuke over there!
Check out the weird assholes!
What are you talking about?
You see what I mean?
Now am I going crazy or is that
one of those creepy slop hurdles?
It's some sort of crop circle.
Yeah, it's one of those things.
Man, that's spooky.
Who would have thought one of them would
pop up in some random field in Morioh?
Wait, Okuyasu.
I've got a weird feeling about this.
Take a close look at the
middle of the circle.
Something's definitely not right here.
We're actually doing this I don't want
to we don't have much of a choice.
Just be careful okay yeah.
So he alive or what well it looks like
something scratched him
on the back of his neck?
But from what I can tell, he just fainted.
Hey, you all right? Wake up!
You know, I don't think I've ever
seen this guy around at school.
Look!
He's finally starting to come to!
Hmm.
How strange.
Oh, you.
What is this place?
What do you mean?
You're in the middle of an
empty field in Budogaoka Morioh.
So then, is this Earth?
I'm not certain why, but I
felt quite unwell last evening.
I must have fallen unconscious
shortly thereafter.
It's past 8.
Given that fact, I estimate I've been
unconscious for nearly 13 Earth hours.
That's a good one man
you really had us going
there i gotta hand it
to you that's one of the
Best jokes i've heard
in a long time if this
whole alien thing doesn't
work out you can totally
become A comedian you're
hilarious you made your
own drop circle and
waited in a bunch of weeks
for Someone to come by
talk about committed to
a bit bravo sir bravo my
stomach i can't breathe? Ah!
Huh?
It's freaking ridiculous!
So what school do you go to, Mr. Alien?
You're just not trying to die, my man!
My home planet was in the Magellanic
Clouds, but it was recently destroyed.
I've journeyed to Earth
to survey its livability.
Moreover, I seek to assess
the amiability of its people.
Piece of advice you should quit
while you're ahead you totally
nailed the prank just ride the
wave and here have a tissue.
Many thanks that was
quite palatable hey look
at the time we don't want
to be late for school.
Oh yeah you're right let's head out!
Did you see the way the guy
scarfed down that tissue?
Even comedians know when to quit.
Aw, no!
The ice cream store's closed!
But this is the only thing that
makes Monday morning's parable!
There's nothing we can do
about it now, so let's just go.
Would you two care for some ice cream?
Well, would you like the cream?
Obviously, but the place is closed.
We're shit out of luck.
That is no reason to give up.
I just so happen to have two here.
It's a quid pro quo for
the tissues you gave me.
Earth seems quite livable
indeed. That it does.
What?
Why do you have ice cream cones
in your bag and how are they cold?
Are the ice of creams unsatisfactory?
That's not the point right now, alien boy!
Who the hell are you?
For real?
Bizarre.
If I recall, I already told you.
Ah,
Ah, you want me to introduce myself.
How could I forget?
You may hereafter address
me as Nu Mikitaka Nushi.
I've lived 216 cycles.
I am the sole pilot of a spaceship and
I also rather enjoy owning house pets.
This is the house mouse that
spends its days in my bag.
He particularly likes it
when I brush his back.
This freaks a stand
user, no doubt about it.
Let's send him to the hospital.
Use your brain, Okuyasu.
Do you really think a
stand user would make up
a story about being from
the Magellanic clouds?
Well, if you're so smart,
what the hell is he?
I don't have the foggiest idea,
but it's time to find out.
Don't eat that ice cream!
You're 216 years old? Yes.
And you're some kind of spaceship pilot?
Yo, why are you copying me?
Huh?
Let's focus here.
So, friend, what's the deal?
Are you telling us you're an alien?
An alien.
An alien, yes.
I should have informed you when we met.
I am indeed an alien.
You know, you're a loony mother...
You said you had a ship.
If it's a genuine flying saucer, it
should be no problem to call it over.
You can do that, right?
Of course,
but it's currently at an
altitude of 1,500,000 kilometers,
so it'd take approximately three days.
So you'll have to wait for a while.
Let me guess, you call it with that watch.
Impressive deductive reasoning.
However, this must stay between we three.
You mustn't share my secret with anyone.
I thought that stunt with a crop
circle was an innocent prank,
but he's off his rocker.
Maybe I should knock this nose-ringed
psycho back to the mothership.
You always let your fists do the talking.
Let's dig a little deeper
before we get violent.
So you're an alien, huh?
Does that mean you're hiding some kind of
ray gun or anti-gravity device in there?
I have both of those things.
But I did not journey to
Earth to engage in conflict,
so I have stored them on my ship.
Ah, come on, Mr. Alien Man!
Why don't you show us
something cool already?
Even your blood is boring.
What alien doesn't come with green blood?
Good point.
Alien blood's always green.
Everyone knows that.
I see.
Are you accusing me of lying?
Hey, take it easy, man.
We're calling you out, asshole.
I can deal with a prank here and there,
but I'll be damned before I waste
my time with a freak like you.
I thought we were going
to do things my way.
Shut up.
It's always better to say it like it is.
Oh, man.
Did a fire break out?
Oh, my God!
Aaaahhh!
W-what's happening?
This sound!
I can't stand this sound!
You have to find a way to stop this sound!
Such a horrible sensation!
I'm allergic to this wretched noise!
Make it stop!
That's enough!
This guy's not right!
We should get as far away
from him as we possibly can!
Yeah, but he's suffering.
We can't just up and abandon
him in this condition.
He said it was allergies.
Just leave him alone.
I'm out of here, Chosuke.
Hey, come back!
Damn, he can be such a dick.
Hey, you doing okay over here?
Please, take me away.
Take me away from this horrid sound!
What the hell?
Take me away!
Whoa, you were telling the truth!
Indeed I was.
I have the ability to transmute
my form into anything.
Hurry, let us take our leave!
I beg you, this sound is
going to split my head in two!
I'll turn into sneakers, so
please put them on and save me!
In return for your help,
I'll do anything you ask!
Hey, are you a stand user?
Whoa, this is some crazy speed!
That's because of your assistance!
My speed and jumping abilities have
been doubled due to our combined power!
An alien!
Just my luck!
What the hell is going on here?!
Hey, you really can't see this?
Huh?
He can't see it.
He's not a stand user.
Then where did his powers come from?
What the hell are you?
You are a stubborn one.
As I've been trying to
tell you, I am an alien.
Fine, just give me a second.
Look, no offense, but it's hard
to wrap my head around all this.
Anyway, I truly appreciate your saving me.
Sirens are mundane here, but the
people on my planet abhor the sound.
The wavelength is very upsetting.
I'd like to repay that kindness.
It's the least I can do for one so brave.
Shall I turn into a fan for you?
Or perhaps a backscratcher to
grab those hard-to-reach places?
I didn't get you out of there
because I wanted something in return!
But if you'll really do anything,
well, who am I to turn you down?
What is it you request of me?
First off, can you really
turn into anything?
Like big or small or even multiples?
Yes, I can transform into nearly anything.
However, becoming complex machinery
or powerful objects is unfeasible.
I read you loud and clear,
and I can tell that we're going
to be the best of friends.
So you want to thank me, right? Yes.
Well, you're in luck, because I just
cooked up a brilliant idea, friend.
Trust me, it's a win-win for
everyone. Win-win? Right!
See, a few weeks ago, I won quite a bit
of spending money in the local lottery.
My mom found out about it, made a
big stink, and froze my account.
Once that woman makes up her mind
about something, your fate is sealed.
Being flat broke during the summer
is the worst, let me tell you.
That's why I need you to turn into these!
Can you?
What are they exactly?
A pair of dice, obviously!
And I'm gonna make some cash with them.
After that, I'll split the winnings
with you, thus creating a win-win.
So how do the dice function? Explain.
Wait, you really don't know what dice are?
I don't. My apologies.
There's nothing to apologize for.
It's super easy to learn.
I'll show you the ropes.
Anyone who likes playing games
goes nuts over these things.
They've got six sides and are
made from a hard material.
The red dot represents
the number one and the
other faces have different
numbers up to six.
I see.
It's starting to make sense.
The five dots represent
the number five, correct?
That's right, Mr.
Alien!
And three dots represent a three.
Yup!
Now try turning into one!
I'm at your service.
Simple.
It's close, but you're a little
too big to pass for a real die.
This is more like it.
You've also got an extra five.
Each face has a different
number from one to six.
The number's on one side, and
its opposite should equal seven.
Oh, my apologies.
Is this better?
That tickles something.
Hey, knock off the laughing.
And dice aren't supposed to talk. Huh?
Oh, come on.
I'll try harder.
I'm a little nervous about this, but...
You look good. Make that great.
We can pull this off.
I'm getting all fired up!
Hope you're ready to lose
some cashola, Rohan Kishibe!
Can't breathe!
Wow, what a surprise.
Now why would Josuke
Higashikata be visiting me?
This is certainly out of the ordinary.
Did you uncover any more dirt on Kira?
Nope, nothing since the last
time we checked in with you.
So, uh, yeah.
Are you all done with your
manga work for the day?
I was wondering if you'd let me take
a peek at the next volume early.
Hmm.
What kind of nonsense are you scheming?
Spit it out, come on.
I should have figured.
Can't get anything past you, Rohan-sensei.
Kay, you got me.
I have an ulterior motive.
I'm begging you, sensei!
Please play Soul with me!
That's it? Soul?
I'm gonna be completely honest.
Summer's finally here, and
I'm totally strapped for cash.
Well, I do have $30,000 on hand.
This is all the money I've got
to my name, but it won't do.
Nowadays,
30,000 yen won't get
you more than a couple
visits to the amusement
park and some snacks.
So I either make some
dough or go flat broke.
Taking risks and thrill-seeking is
the very foundation of being young.
That's what I think at least.
You agree, don't you?
Let me be frank.
I've despised you from
the moment I met you.
There's absolutely no
reason for me to waste
my precious time playing Soul with you.
I guess you're right.
I mean, you're not
exactly hurting for cash.
I don't know what I was thinking.
Why would you want to play a game with me?
Even so, count me in. Huh?
Seriously? You'll do it?
I don't dislike games.
In fact, I'm intrigued.
Come around back whenever you're ready.
We're gonna have a great
time, Rohan-sensei.
Do these rules work for you?
Yeah, looks good each chip
is worth a thousand yen,
and you must roll three dice into the
bowl if one falls out you lose Got it.
All right.
I'll place the rules here.
So they're in plain view.
Okay, let's get this party.
Wait
We won't be using those dice. Huh?
We'll use these.
They're a set I found in the house.
Oh
Really?
That's interesting.
Is there some reason that you
don't want to use my dice?
Not really I feel inclined to play with my
own is all just a whim
when I mentioned I was!
Intrigued it wasn't by the prospect
of playing Soul no no Josuke I was!
Intrigued by the prospect of swiping
30,000 yen from you now when you lose!
Against me I expect you to pay in full I
don't care how much we've been through!
Understand?
Perfect!
The dice he found are actually the alien!
I managed to sneak them into his
house when he wasn't paying attention!
I'm such a bad boy.
It won't be a ton, but you're about
to fund my summer Fugo, Rohan-sensei!
Now then, shall we determine
who gets to go first?
Four.
Yes!
Looks like you're up first. Roll the dice.
Ow!
Ow, ow, ow!
I banged my hand into the table!
Place your bet and roll
the dice. Yeah, right.
Uh, guess I'll start things
off by betting 2,000 yen.
So I'll throw down two chips.
Alright, so will I.
If I roll a one, a two, and a
three, I'll have to pay double.
So I need to avoid those
numbers at all costs.
One and two and three, keep
those rolls away from me!
The first roll calls for a light
touch, sort of like a practice toss.
Here we go. Gently.
Okay, looking good!
What?
It's an omen!
Triple sixes, aka an omen!
Josuke wins five times what he wagered!
Hey, don't start that way, dumbass!
What I meant to say was...
I can't believe I had such dumb luck!
A triple six and five times the winnings?
How's that even happen?
To the untrained eye, it almost looks
like I'm cheating even though I'm not!
Somehow, you already managed
to win 10,000 yen from me.
At any rate, let's continue.
If I'm not mistaken, I'm next.
I want to get back what
I've lost, so I think...
I'll wager 10 chips.
You sure about this?
And here we go.
A one, a two, and a three.
Rohan must pay double
the amount of his wager.
He's taken the hustle way too far.
It's getting obvious.
Does this alien know the
meaning of the word restraint?
Shit, biscuits.
If this keeps up, he'll bust us for sure.